How you doing?
The first thing on this I'm going to do is show you how to pick out ingredients.
First of all you have the tomato, the tomato needs to be nice and firm all the way around.
You want there to be no bruising or no big dents and you want it to be bright red.
The avocado for the guacamole now you want this avocado to be nice and tender.
You don't want it to be real hard or anything like that, you want to be able to push this circle button on the very top to push that button in and if sinks in like that then that it is nice and firm in the inside.
You got your mango we want to make sure that your mango is pretty tender so if you push it down you can go in but you don't want it to be so soft where you thumb goes right through.
You want it to be kind of firm but at the same time you want it to be also tender.
Same thing with your lime you want to see a nice tenderness going all the way around it and you want it to be bright green.
If you see any browning or it is kind of hard that means that it is a older lime and you don't want to go around that lime you want it to stay away from that.
With your Serrano's you also want them to be bright green and just look around and make sure that there is no holes or bruising.
You onions are kind of hard to tell what your onions look likes because it has a wrap around it you just want to go around the onion and kind of feel and make sure there is no holes or anything like that and the same thing with the shallots.
You want to go around and make sure there is no holes and that is how you can pick ingredient for making this meal.